Now that the tuning job has finished,
优化作业运行完毕了
you can see that we've got a whole bunch of output here.
可以在这里看到大量输出结果
This output describes the results of our tuning Job,
这个输出描述了优化作业的结果
and one of the most important bits is all the way
最重要的信息是
down here where it says best training job.
最底下的 BestTrainingJob 部分
You can see that this is an entry in the resulting dictionary
这是结果字典中的一个条目
which contains the name of the tuning job that performed the best.
其中包含最佳优化作业的名称
So, we're going to need that name so that we can create
我们需要该名称 以便使用与此训练作业
a model from the training artifacts associated with this training job.
相关的训练工件创建一个模型
Now, if you don't want to go through this output and copy and paste,
如果你不想浏览此输出并复制名称
you can get a copy of this object by using
可以使用 sagemaker_client 的
the describe hyperparameter tuning job method of the SageMaker client.
describe_hyper_parameter_tuning_job 方法获得此对象的副本
All you have to do is provide it with the name of
只需提供要获取其信息的
the tuning job whose information you'd like to get.
优化作业的名称即可
Now, tuning job info contains all of the information up here.
tuning_job_info 包含这里的所有信息
In particular, it has the name of the best training job.
尤其是包含最佳训练作业的名称
Using that name, we can use the describe training job method,
我们可以根据该名称使用 describe_training_job 方法
to get information about that training job.
获取关于该训练作业的信息
In particular, we can get access to the model artifacts which are stored on S3.
我们可以访问存储在 S3 上的模型工件
Once we have a URI to the Model Artifacts,
获得模型工件的 URI 后
we can use that to construct a model object.
我们可以使用该 URI 构建模型对象
Remember then in SageMaker,
在 SageMaker 中
a model is a collection of data that contains the container that is meant to be used
模型是一个数据集合 其中包含要在推理过程中使用的容器
during inference in addition to the model artifacts that were created during training.
以及在训练过程中创建的模型工件
Once we've created the model object,
创建模型对象后
we can create a batch transform job to test our model.
我们可以创建批转换作业来测试模型
To create a batch transform job,
创建批转换作业的步骤
we do the same thing as we did in the previous notebook.
与在之前的 notebook 中的步骤一样
In that we just create a data structure that it contains
我们创建一个数据结构
all the information about the batch transform job we wish to create,
其中包含关于要创建的批转换作业的所有信息
and then we ask SageMaker to execute that batch transform
然后要求 SageMaker 执行该批转换作业
job and wait for the results to see how well our model is doing.
并等待结果 看看模型的表现如何
Now that the batch transform job has finished up,
批转换作业运行完毕后
we can copy the results to
我们可以将结果
our notebook instance and then take a look and see how well it did.
复制到 notebook 实例中 看看效果如何